电视:这就是我们调查活动的一部分,
TV: And that's why for our part of the investigation, New York's finest:
纽约最佳匹萨饼店.
Pizzerias that is.
凯特:你相信地方新闻台播的这些垃圾节目吗?
Kate: Do you believe the garbage they have on local news?
迈克:哦,是的.谁是名列第二的匹萨饼呢,是耶西蒂还是安东尼奥呢?
Mike: Oh yeah, I know.Who was number two, was it Jessetti or Antonio?
电视:据报道,
TV: Still ahead, Record snowstorms are due to hit local ski resort areas
特大暴风雪将与本周末袭击当地的滑雪度假区.
this weekend.
凯特:哦迈克,滑雪不是很有意思吗?
Kate: Oh, Mike, doesn't skiing sound like fun?
迈克:呃,什么才是有意思的吗?
Mike: Uh, you know what sounds like a lot of fun?
就是花两美元买纳吉尔匹萨店的一个外卖尝一尝.
It's two for one take-out thing to taste at Nagel's.
凯特:我们还是出去走走,去吹一吹新鲜,寒冷的空气.
Kate: We'd be outdoor, the cold fresh wind in our faces.
迈克:好的.匹萨饼来了后,我们就带到后院里去吃.
Mike: That's fine, when the pizza gets here we will take it in the backyard.
凯特:迈克.我是认真的.
Kate: Mike, I am serious.
迈克:凯特.你觉得我有钱去滑雪吗?
Mike: Kate, you think I can afford a ski-trip?
凯特:我有钱.上次做模特挣的钱我还剩一些.
Kate: I can, I got some money left at my last modeling job.
迈克:我不想领你的情,
Mike: look, don't take this in a patronizing way,
我只是想找一个能为你这个小女人付钱的方式.
but I do like to pay for the little woman.
凯特:那好吧,我 建议你找一个.
Kate: Well, then I suggest you find one.
迈克:哦,听我说,
Mike: Aw, look, Kate,
凯特,我的意思是,如果我能支付,
what I am saying is just that I would feel a lot more comfortable doing
我会感到更舒服的,比如说我们出去吃顿饭什么的.
things that I can afford.Like taking us out to dinner.
凯特:我厌倦了,每次你吃儿童套餐的时候,我只能躲在洗手间里.
Kate: I am tired of hiding in the bathroom while you're taking happy meals.
凯特:好了,每当你得到海盗帽的时候,我也没听见你抱怨什么.好吧,那我们就去滑雪.
Mike: Well, I did not hear you complain when you got the pirate hit.Alright
alright I will take you skiing
凯特:好啊,好啊!
Kate: Yes, yes!
迈克:但是我来付钱,就这么定了.
Mike: But I am paying and that's that.
凯特:谁付钱还不是一样啊?
Kate: What does it matter who pays.
迈克:因为我是个男人,凯特;还有就是我有自尊.
Mike: Because Kate I m a man, and if nothing else, I have got my pride.
迈克:哦,求你了,求你了!开萝尔,借我些钱吧.
Mike: Oh, please, please, please!Carol, borrow me some money.
开萝尔:我送你三个字:没门.
Carol: I have 3 words for you.No way.
迈克:这只是两个字.
Mike: That's only two.
开萝尔:没门,大傻瓜.
Carol: No way.Stump-head.
迈克:好,好,好,开萝尔,我会用自己的钱去滑雪的.
Mike: Fine, fine, fine, Carol, I can finish this trip out of my own pocket!
卢克:等一会.
Luke: Wakes up late.
迈克:嘿,能告诉我"白山度假旅馆"的电话号码吗?
Mike: Hey, can I have the number for the White Mountain Watch please?
谢谢.
Thank you.
卢克:迈克,你为什么不让凯特付钱呢?
Luke: Mike, why don't you just let Kate pay?
迈克:听着,这种事太复杂你还理解不了.
Mike: Look, this is far too complicated for you to understand.
卢克:呃,迈克付钱:大男人!
Luke: Huh, Mike pays: Big man!
凯特付钱:抬不起头!
Kate pays: Big Wuss!
迈克:这真是太复杂了?!
Mike: That is pretty doggone complicated?!
迈克打电话:嗨,您可以告诉我你们那里最便宜,最吸引人的房间多少钱吗?300美元?
Mike on phone: Hi, could you please tell me how much your cheapest but most
impressive room is?Three hundred dollars
哦,有没有更便宜点的,比如发生过谋杀案的房间?275?
Oh, don't you have something cheaper, like a room somebody was murdered in?
哦好的,还有没有别的?免费房间?
That's two seventy five?Yeah well do you have anything else?A free room?
但是让我带20个付费客人?好,好,我能办到.
But only if I bring 20 paying customers with me?Ok I will take it!
好,好,对,西沃带20个人的团队,
Yeah, yeah, that's right, Siever.
好的,我预定,是的,莫里斯.
Party 20, book Danielle, fine, book it Morris.
迈克对卢克:嘿,卢克,
Mike to Luke: Hey, Luke, uh,
呃,这个周末想去滑雪吗,仅需50美元?
how would you like to go skiing this weekend for only fifty bucks?
卢克:哦,我一直在存钱呢,
Luke: Well, I have been saving my allowance, but one question:
不过有个问题:你去哪里去找另外19个傻瓜为你们滑雪付帐呢?
Where are we gonna
find nineteen other saps stupid enough to pay for your skiing trip
本:你想让我邀请整个高中象棋俱乐部的人去滑雪?
Ben: You want me to invite the entire Duree High chess club skiing?
迈克,象棋俱乐部里都是些书呆子,他们不想滑什么雪的.
Mike, the chess club is the valley of the geefers, these guys won't wanna ski.
迈克:不过,本,他们听你的.你是队长啊.
Mike: But, Ben, they'll listen to you.You're their president.
本:我辞过职,可他们都哭了.
Ben: I tried to resign.They started crying.
迈克:好,我就喜欢带这些文雅的人出去.
Mike: Well, they're just like the kinda gentle souls that I'd like to chaperone.
本:迈克,这些人跟滑雪太不相称了.
Ben: Mike, these guys are too uncoordinated to ski.
上周,里奥普拉特的脚趾就夹到滑板里了.
Last week, Leo Platte's toe got his toe stuck in his fly!
迈克:没问题!太好了!
Mike: It's not problem!It's perfect!
他们不必滑雪,只要玩就行了!
They don't have to ski, the just have to pay!
本:那我能得到什么?
Ben: So what's in this for me?
迈克:哦,你会在严寒中锻炼你的鼻子.
Mike: Well, you'll have Jack Frost,
另外,你还可以找到迷人的滑雪姑娘与你同行…
nipping at your nose and you'll have a gorgeous ski buddy nipping at your...
本:18个人报了名,我让他们全都付的现金!
Ben: Eighteen sign-ups and I made them all pay cash!
如果没事的话,
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要去缝个布兜,贴身放到夹克里.
I'll have to go and sew some lipid patches in my jacket.
迈克:大功告成!
Mike: Mission Accomplished!
卢克:太好,
Luke: Alright, but one question:
还有个问题:你带这18个笨手本脚的家伙去,
What are you and Kate gonna do starting by eating at DuFei with cheese
你和凯特还能做什么呢?
in their braces?
迈克:说的对.
Mike: You're right, now I don't know who is gullible enough to chaperone
现在我不知道谁能被骗来给我当一回"牧羊犬"呢?
on a herd of nerds?
德怀特:那个高个子说:鸭子-噢-鸭子!我也是鸭子!
Dwight: The tall guy said: Duck-o-ree-dee duck!Duck for me too!
两个人:笑.
Both: laugh.
迈克:嘿,伙计们,笑什么呢?
Mike: Hi guys, what's going on?
德怀特:哦,我要带开萝尔去瑞典电影节.
Dwight: Oh I am taking Carol to the Swedish film festival.
开萝尔:有部电影叫:.
Carol: We're seeing: My life is a dog.
迈克:哦,开萝尔,你为什么要花钱看呢?你就是啊!
Mike: Oh Carol, Why would I pay money to see that?You live it!
开萝尔:实话对你说吧,
Carol: For your information,
我和德怀特再也不能忍受你们这样对待我了.
Dwight and I are getting pre-fed-up with the way you guys treat me.
德怀特:说的对!我听够了.
Dwight: That's right!I've had an earful.
我不想听到你把女朋友再比作一部瑞典电影.
And I don't wanna hear you compare my girlfriend to a Swedish film again.
你听到了吗,软糖小子?
You know what I mean jellybean?
迈克:哦,我们当然自惭形愧.
Mike: Well, uh, we're of course ashamed of ourselves.
嘿,我来补偿怎么样?呃?
Hey how about I make it up to ya?Huh?
这个周末,我们去滑雪,
What would you say to a ski trip this weekend,
好吗?到"白山度假旅馆",100美元.
at the White Mountain lodge for one hundred bucks!
德怀特:哦,不,
Dwight: Oh no please, the ski trip is enough,
谢谢了,我滑雪就够了.我不能接受你的100美元.
I could not possibly accept one hundred bucks.
迈克:不,德怀特,你来付钱.
Mike: No, Dwights, you would pay.
德怀特:哦,那好多了了.
Dwight: Oh that's better.Ok, yea, count us in.
好的,算我们俩.要带自己的滑雪裤吗?
Do we bring our own leather hosing?
迈克:不用.你可以租,那里有个滑雪裤租赁站.德怀特,
Mike: No, no, you can rent, there is a leather hosing stand.
德怀特,不过,我差点忘了最重要的了!
Dwight, Dwight, but, uh, I almost forgot the best part!
你要带20个年轻的象棋选手坐巴士去.
See, you'll be driving up on a bus with 20 teenage chess players.
德怀特:Yippi-Ya Yo-ka-ye!
Dwight: Yippi-Ya Yo-ka-ye!
迈克:我是怎么想的呢?
Mike: Well, what was I thinking?
你要在他们上车的时候用名单对一下名字.
You will have to check their names off a list as they get on the bus.
德怀特:开玩笑,这么便宜的事,数他们的牙齿都可以.
Dwight: You're kidding, for a cheap ski trip I'll check their teeth!
迈克:好,太好了!
Mike: Okay, well great!
还有一件事:我们需要跟开萝尔说一下,
Just one other thing: we need to tell Carol about this,
让她觉得这是你的主意.坐巴士去会是一个惊喜,
make her think it was your idea.
女人总是喜欢这类玩意.
And the bus ride will be a surprise, women love that kinda stuff.
德怀特:迈克,你对我太好了.
Dwight: Mike, you're so good to me.
德怀特:亲爱的?我决定这个周末去滑雪.
Dwight: Honey?I decided we go skiing this weekend.
开萝尔:和你?
Carol: With you?
德怀特:而且没有什么象棋棋手!
Dwight: And no chess players!
开萝尔:哦,德怀特,你对我太好了!
Carol: Oh, Dwight, you're so good to me!
麦琪:迈克,
Maggie: Mike, you wanna take Ben and Luke and a bunch of teenagers on
你想带本和卢克还有一帮少年人这个周末去滑雪吗?
a weekend ski trip?
迈克:呃-噢.
Mike: Uh-huh
杰森:我们也许有个大问题,年轻人.
Jason: We're gonna have a big problem with that, young man.
迈克:哦,德怀特和开萝尔也去.
Mike: Well, Dwight and Carol are coming.
杰森:玩的开心,儿子!
Jason: Have a good time, son!
麦琪:杰森:开萝尔能去我感觉好多了,
Maggie: Jason, I look I feel better knowing that Carol's going but didn't
但你答应的也太快了吧?
you cave in a little easier?
杰森:我不是答应的快,麦琪,
Jason: I did not cave Maggie, I calculated quickly.
我是脑子转的快.自从克莉丝出生以来,周末只有我们俩这还是第一次.
I have just bought us our first weekend allowance since Chrissy was born!
克莉丝:爸爸,我上楼起,你能把水龙头打开吗?
Chrissy: Daddy, can you turn on the water when I get upstairs?
麦琪:宝贝,你做什么呢?
Maggie: Eddie, what are you doing?
克莉丝:和水泥啊.
Chrissy: Making Cement?
杰森:哇,哇,
Jason: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇.这个周末你去赫尔麦斯奶奶家去和水泥好吗?
How would you like to make some cement at grandma Hermes's this week?
克莉丝:太好了!你要是早这么说就好了,我都把沙子弄到楼上来了!
Chrissy: Great!I just wish you'd said something before I slipped the gravel upstairs
女人:你好.(外语,也许是法语,意思是我来了)(外语)这间房子有什么不同之处吗?
Woman: Bonjour, (foreign language probably French meaning I am here) (foreign language) Is there something
different about this room
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: No.?
女人:太差了!
Woman: Too bad!
麦琪:你的头发有什么不同之处吗?
Maggie: Is there something different about your hair?
女人:哦,没有.
Woman: Oh, no, no
杰森:嘿,嘿,嘿.
Jason: Hey, hey, Hey.
杰森:这个小家伙是谁啊?
Jason: Who is this little fella?
女人:他是我儿子,马克斯!
Woman: This is my son, Max!
杰森:很好,握握手,马克斯.
Jason: Yeah, give me five Max.
马克斯:(拍打杰森)噢!
Max: (slaps Jason) Yeah!
女人:他真的很喜欢你.他一般对自己的爷爷才这样呢.
Woman: He is really like you.He usually does this to grandparents.As usual.
像往常一样,我们打算出去.你能不能帮着照料一下我们的房子?
we're going away this week, could you keep an eye oin our house?
拿拿信件,报纸,牛奶什么的.
Taking the mail, the papers, the goat cheese,
杰森:嘿,你们一出去,我们就上工.
Jason: Hey but once you get outta town, we're through.
女人:是吗?宝贝,来个吻别.
Woman: Oh no?kiss kiss bye-bye?
麦琪:哦,不会是这样吧?
Maggie: Rich-rich, gag-gag?
凯特:这真是太好了!看看这房子,
Kate: I thought it was wonderful!Look at the bungalow, it's huge!
真大啊!20个人都可以睡在这里!
You could sleep twenty people here!
迈克:是的,我们真幸运!
Mike: Yeah, with any luck!
凯特:我真不相信你能为我们俩预订了这个大的房子!
Kate: I can't believe you got us an enormous place all to ourselves!
迈克:哦,是的,实际上是的.
Mike: Well, yea, actually, uh
凯特:那不是一路上跟着我们来这里的那辆巴士吗?
Kate: Isn't this the same bus of kids tat followed us all the way up here?
迈克:是的,就是那辆车,凯特.
Mike: Yeah, it is, listen Kate, I got a kinda confession I wanna make to you.
我要向你坦白一件事.你看,我安排了一帮孩子跟我们一起滑雪.
You see, I sort of arranged for a small group of kids to come join us.
凯特:和我们一起?
Kate: Join us?
迈克:是的.不过他们是举止文明,
Mike: Yes, but they're very well behaved, small, well-chaperoned.
而且很听话的孩子.我们只管玩我们的.
We'll hardly notice.
小流氓:好了,太空迷们!让我们疯狂吧!
Hooligan: Okay Space Fans!At once, let's get stupid!
迈克:对不起,本,本?这是怎么了?本,这不是象棋俱乐部的孩子?
Mike: Excuse me, Ben, Ben?What's going on?Ben this can't be the Chess Club?
本:你怎么看出来的?
Ben: How can you tell?
迈克:什么?嘿,嘿,嘿,
Mike: What, hey, hey, hey you, If I challenged your queen with my rook,
你,如果我用车将你的军,你会怎么办?
what would you do?
小流氓:把你倒立起来,许个愿吧?!
Hooligan: Turn you upside down and make a wish?!
本:得了,迈克!
Ben: Come on Mike!I did not want to spend the weekend with Nerds on Ice!
我可不想跟一群不会玩雪的笨蛋过周末!所以我邀请了整个学校最疯狂的一些人.
So I invented the biggest party in the whole school.
迈克:有这些疯狗,我和凯特还能好好地过周末吗?哦,一群疯狗!
Mike: How am I supposed to have a nice weekend with Kate with all these horn dogs, uh, horny dogs or whatever!
本:说的对,说的对,
Ben: You're right, you're right, I see your point.
我知道你的意思了.我们送凯特乘下班车回去.
Let's send Kate home on the next bus.
迈克:我说的是下象棋的那些人!
Mike: I said chess club members!
本:哦,还真有一个."酸舌头"的佛莱特.
Ben: Well, you got one.Leo Lime-tongue Flat neck.
迈克:酸舌头?
Mike: Lime-tongue?
本:是的,他的舌头是绿的.他只吃绿东西.
Ben: Well, he's tongue is green.He only eats green things.
卢克:哦,这就是我们生活的理由!
Luke: Well, that's the explanation we can live with!
小流氓:很乐意帮你上蜡!
Hooligan: I'll be glad to wax them for ya!
凯特:哦,我的滑板不上蜡.
Kate: Oh, I don't my skis waxed.
小流氓:我指的不是你的滑板.
Hooligan: I'm not talking about your skis.
凯特:迈克!
Kate: Mike!
德怀特:好了,我们终于到了.对了,迈克,你可没说让我开巴士啊.
Dwight: Okay, our present account of, by the way, Mike, you did not mention that
I had to drive the bus
迈克:德怀特,不应该你来开巴士的!
Mike: Dwight, you were supposed to drive the bus!
德怀特:哦,好吧,怪不得我开车走的时候,那个家伙老骂我呢.
Dwight: Oh, well, that's why that guy was cussing at me while we drove away.
凯特:不,我不会参加任何所谓热火朝天的活动.
Kate: No, I will NOT participate in anything called a Moon-o-thon.
房间呢,我要做的就是离开这些…狂呼乱叫的疯子,
Where are the rooms, all I wanna do is get away from these...
他们竟然会在车顶上跳舞.
screaming banshees, they're dancing on top of the bus.
迈克:不,不,不,
Mike: No, no, no, no, Carol.You cannot go hide in your room!
开萝尔,你不能只躲在自己的房间里!你和德怀特是来帮忙的!
You and Dwight are here to chaperone!
开萝尔:(歇斯底里地)哈?
Carol: (Hysteric) Huh?
德怀特:是的,我们谈了环境,谈了滑雪裤,可从来没说要帮忙的?!
Dwight: Yeah, we talked into hygiene, we talked leather hose, but there is no mention
of chaperoning
迈克:哇,哇,
Mike: Whoa whoa, excuse me?
对不起?我费尽周折给你和开萝尔优惠.
I went outta my way to get you and Carol this bargain trip?
现在我最需要你的时候,你却没有半分钟去照料一下那些活蹦乱跳的孩子?
And now when I need you the most,
you don't have a couple of extra minutes to keep an eye on some fun-starved
kids?
德怀特:是的.我很痛苦.自私,自私,自私!
Dwight: That's right.I've been in pain.Selfish, selfish, selfish!
迈克:好多了,好了.
Mike: Much better, ok, now, come here.
现在过来.男孩的房间在右边那里,女孩的房间在左边.
The boys room is over here on the right, and the girls' on the left.
不管你做什么,千万别和哪个大个子下象棋.
Whatever you do, don't play chess with the big guy.
德怀特:你说够了没有?
Dwight: Could I have your attention?
开萝尔:迈克?
Carol: Mike?This time you've pushed things too far!
这次你玩的太过分了!
I only came up here because Dwight said you invited us out of goodness
我只所以来是因为德怀特说你是真心诚意地要求我们出来的.
of your heart!
迈克:开萝尔,你认识我20你了,你觉得那是我吗?
Mike: Carol, you know me for 20 years.Does that sound like me?
开萝尔:不.
Carol: No.
迈克:现在,马上去吧!
Mike: Now, go, shift!
凯特:迈克?就算我过时了,可20个孩子闹哄哄地,跟我想像的浪漫周末可不搭边啊.
Kate: Mike?Call me old-fashioned, but twenty kids pouncing the bell hop is not
exactly my idea of a romantic weekend
迈克::每个人好像很开心啊?别担心那些孩子.
Mike: Everyone seems to be enjoying it?Don't worry about the kids.
他们很快乐的.
They'll be fun.
酸舌头:西沃先生?
Lime tongue: Mr.Siever?
迈克:你是谁?
Mike: Who are you?
凯特:天啊!
Kate: God!
迈克:我一会就过去,酸舌头.
Mike: I'll be with you in a second, Lime Tongue.
过来,会好的.
Come here, it's gonna be fine, Carol is in charge of the kids,
开萝尔负责这些孩子.他们一滑上雪,我们就不用操心了.
we wont even notice them once they've hit the slope.
酸舌头:哦,我就来说这个的,
Lime tongue: Oh that's what I came to tell you sir, there is no snow.
先生.这里没雪.滑雪场都关闭了.
The area is completely shut down.
这大概和热带低气压有关系.
Something to do with tropical depression "Urve"
两个人:没雪?
Both: No snow?
酸舌头:你知道吗?我也很兴奋,
Lime tongue: You know what!I am excited too, I am allergic to snow.
我对雪过敏.现在我们可以拿出棋盘来杀两局了吧.
Now we can reak up the chess boards and have a "hoot nanny".
迈克:听着,你的对手的名字叫开萝尔,好吗?她不在这里,她在房间里试化妆品呢1
Mike: Look, your hoot master's named Carol, okay?She's not even here, she's tested the
ear wax
凯特:迈克.如果这些孩子不滑雪,他们会把这里闹翻天的!
Kate: Mike, if these kids can't ski, they'll tear this place apart!
迈克:凯特,凯特,放松!
Mike: Kate, Kate, relax!That's the beauty of my plans.
这才是我们计划的精彩之处.这不是我们的问题,是开萝尔的.
It is not our problem, it's Carol's.
迈克:开萝尔,怎么了!??
Mike: Carol, what happened!??
开萝尔:我脚扭伤了.
Carol: It's my ankle.
卢克:她在冰上滑了一跤.
Luke: She slipped on some ice.
迈克:什么,什么冰?这里没冰!
Mike: What, what Ice?There's no ice!
酸舌头:我把芬达饮料撒了.
Lime tongue: I spilled my Fanta.
德怀特:别害怕,我马上叫医生来.你再也不用去管那帮人了.
Dwight: Fear nothing, but I am gonna get a doctor, you're in no condition to
chaperone
凯特:哦,"愿意为小女人付帐先生",
Kate: Well, Mr-I-like-to-pay-for-the-little-women,
看来你要负责了.
looks like you're in charge now?
酸舌头:我说,你为什么不豁出去,也闹个底朝天呢?
Lime tongue: Say, why don't you ditch Brillow-head and let's get stupid?
麦琪:哦,杰森,只有我和你在这个大房子里了,只有我们自己.
Maggie: Ooh, Jason, just you and I in this big house.All by ourselves.
杰森:哦,是的.
Jason: Uh-huh
麦琪:那我们做什么呢?
Maggie: Whatever shall we do?
杰森:哦,我不知道.
Jason: Well, I don't know.
杰森:哦,这是从克里德马丁家传来的,一定是他们家那该死的警报.
Jason: Well, that 's coming from the Creed Martin, must be their stupid house alarm
麦琪:有人闯进去了?
Maggie: Did somebody break in?
杰森:不是.我希望如此.也许他们会关掉的.
Jason: Not that I hope so..Maybe they will shut the alarm off.
杰森打电话:是的,是的,是的.我是报告你们罗宾汉街17号的警报器一直在响.
Jason on phone: Yeah, Yes, yes, I am calling to report a house alarm going
off at 17, Robinhood lane
我知道,我的嗓音很好听,
Yes, I know I have a very nice speaking voice, thank you.
谢谢.我并不是要你们过来?!
No, I don't want you to come over?!
我只是希望你去通知警察.你会派人过来吗?几时?20分钟或6个小时?
I just would like you to notify the police.Could you send somebody over?
不,这不太荒唐了…呃?哈!
When?Between twenty minutes and six hours?No, that's ridicule..Uh?Huh!
杰森对麦琪:我们处在危机中,那个"911"的接线员还跟我调情呢.
Jason to Maggie: We got a crisis and the 911 operator is flirting with me.
麦琪:哦,那她可真没有职业素养?!
Maggie: Well, that's unprofessional of her?!
杰森:是个男人.
Jason: Him.
酸舌头:(唱歌)有个人把蛋糕抛弃在雨中 我想不会拿起它 因我花了长时间去拿
Lime tongue (singing):Someone left the cake out in the rain I don't think
that I can take itCuz I took so long to take it
我还没有制作配方,再来! 哦,不…
And I'll never have that recipe, again!Oh noooooo!
酸舌头:再来一遍,各位!
Lime tongue: One more time everybody!
迈克:好的!已经9点半了,各位?该睡觉了.
Mike: O-kay!Is it 9:30 everybody?It's time to turn in.
金发女孩:首先,这里没雪,
Blonde girl: First there is no snow, and now I have to go to bed early?
我还要早睡吗?你比我妈还糟糕!
You are worse than my mother!
小流氓:我花了钱来过愉快的周末.我就是要玩个痛快.
Hooligan: I paid for a fun weekend, and I am gonna have fun, whether I party,
要不然的话,我把你的脸打扁!晚安!
or snow-plough your face!Good night!
德怀特:哦,我抱你进房间,亲爱的,我还要去查房呢.
Dwight: Oh, carrying you into the room my darling, I do have to go do a bed check.
开萝尔:这真浪漫,就想的场景.
Carol: This is so romantic, just like in Gone with the wind.
开萝尔:我的瑞德!
Carol: My Red!
德怀特:我的斯嘉丽!
Dwight: My Scarlet.
卢克:我的天啊!!
Luke: My God!!
凯特:我们独处的时间连两分钟都没有.
Kate: We have not had two minutes alone.
我把时间都花到绿舌头身上了!
I have spent more time with green tongue!
酸舌头:酸舌头.
Lime tongue: Lime tongue.
凯特:想个办法啊!
Kate: Do something!
迈克:好的,我来想.
Mike: Go, suck an avocado!
酸舌头:哦,宝贝!
Lime tongue: Ooh, Baby!
迈克:听我说,凯特,
Mike: Look, Kate, look, I know that the trip not lucky on the start.
我知道这次旅行一开始就不顺.不过,现在我们两个人了.
But we alone now.
你觉得我们冲点热可可,依偎在火边怎么样?
So, what do you say we make some hot coco, we snuggle by the fire.
凯特:哦,太好了!
Kate: Oh, great!
迈克:好的,来吧,呵呵呵.
Mike: Ok, Come on.Hehehe.
大家:冲,冲,冲,冲.
All: Go, go, go, go.
凯特:怎么了?
Kate: What's that?
迈克:只是风而已.
Mike: It's just the wind.
德怀特:哦,我要睡觉了.孩子们都在床上玩混合双打呢.
Dwight: Oh, I am gonna turn in now, kids are all in bed playing Mix Doubles for cheesy.
凯特:混合双打?
Kate: Mix Doubles?
迈克:在他们床上?
Mike: In their beds?
德怀特:是的,他们还要玩个通宵呢.
Dwight: Yeah, so it's up to about Shrimps and Skins.
凯特:他最好确保没人得分才好.
Kate: He better makes sure no one scores.
麦琪:杰森,我说了无数遍了,我们为什么不去住酒店呢?
Maggie: Jason, for the umpteenth time, why don't we just check into a hotel?
杰森:麦琪,我们不能因为我们的邻居是聋子就去住昂贵的酒店.
Jason: Maggie, we are not gonna check into an expensive hotel just because
我还是想想怎么花这36块半吧.
we have Godless neighbours.I better think what to do with my 36:50.
麦琪:哦…那你为什么把这声音放在心上了?假装这是海浪?!
Maggie Oh...Why don't you just block the sound out of your mind?Pretend it's the ocean?!
杰森:麦琪, 海浪并没有伤害我的听力
Jason: Oh, Maggie, the ocean does not make my ears bleed.
杰森打电话:喂,对,今天晚上,为了这个警报器我已经打了好几次电话了.对,我就是那个嗓音好听的人.
Jason on phone: Hello, yea, I've called several times tonight about this house alarm going
off, yes; I am the one with the nice speaking voice
噢,太好了,警铃公司派人过来.
Oh great, good, the alarm company's sending somebody over.That's terrific.
那太好了,什么时候?星期一早上?!!!
When; Monday morning?!!!
你听我说:我就是那个强盗,正站在他们的饭厅里.
Listen to me: I am the burglar.
盯着他们的一柜子瓷器.
I am standing in the dining room looking at the china cabinet and if you
你们不马上派人过来的话,那我可就要动手了!
don't send somebody right away, the gravy boat goes!
快派人过来…好,什么时候?20分钟到6小时???我…
Sending somebody over... Alright, when?Twenty minutes to six hours???I uph!
麦琪:等等.别做傻事.
Maggie: Wait a minute.Don't do anything foolish.
杰森:你觉得我像是要去做傻事吗?
Jason: Do you think I look like I am about do something foolish?
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
警察:你认识这个傻瓜,呃?
Police: So you know this clown, huh?
麦琪:警官,他不是傻瓜.
Maggie: Officer, this is no clown,
他是爱我的丈夫和受人尊敬的精神病医生.
This is a loving husband and a respected psychiatrist.
警察:怪不得他穿着睡衣爬上梯子,
Police: Which is why he was up a ladder in his pyjamas trying to slap
试图拍打你邻居家的防盗警报器.
shack your neighbour's burglar alarm.
杰森:你这么说,显得我很傻.但我…
Jason: When you put it that way it sounds silly.But I had...
麦琪:警官…就是那个警报器,让我丈夫失去了理智.
Maggie: Officer... it's that alarm, it's driving my husband out of his mind.
警察:原来是这么回事.
Police: A sure trip I am sure.
麦琪:你不能做点什么吗?
Maggie: Can't you do something?
警察:我可以那枪把打他?
Police: I could pistol-whip him?
麦琪:不,不,是那个警报器.
Maggie: No, no, about the alarm.
警察:哦,我的搭档在干着呢,夫人.
Police: Well, uh, my partner is already on that, Ma'am.
杰森:谢谢,谢谢,谢谢.你是个王子.
Jason: Thank you, thank you, thank you, you're a prince.
警察:清醒点,清醒点.
Police: Cool it, cool it.
我说老兄,
Look pal, that stuff may work on 911 operator,
用这一套骗骗"911"接线员还可以.但我不是那种人.
but I am a different breed of cat.
警察对麦琪:夫人.
Police to Maggie: Ma'am.
杰森:嘿,嘿,噢,噢,警官!
Jason: Hey, hey, oooh, oooh, officer!
凯特:你知道整个灾难是怎么发生的吗?
Kate: Do you know why this whole disaster happened?
就是因为你坚持不让我付帐.
Because you could have let me pay for a simple trip.
迈克:噢,不,凯特,
Mike: Uh, Look, Kate, Kate, if it would have just snowed,
凯特,如果正好下雪,又如果本带的是象棋俱乐部的孩子,
and if Ben had just invited the Chess Club,
又如果开萝尔没有滑倒在饮料水上,又如果酸舌头还没生出来.
Carol hadn't slipped on that Soda, and Lime tongue had not been born!
凯特:迈克!就因为你那该死的自尊,这个周末谁也没玩好.
Kate: Mike!Because of your stupid pig-headed pride, nobody had fun this weekend.
开萝尔:哦,噢…噢…噢…!(骑着德怀特)
Carol: Oh, oooh, oooooh, hooooh!(as riding Dwight)
卢克:我希望在开车回家之前,她能下来.
Luke: I hope she dismounts him before he drives us home!
凯特:下次,谁有钱,谁就付帐!
Kate: Next time, whoever has the money, pays!
本:我来接!
Ben: I'll get it!
酸舌头:坏消息!暴风雪来了!道路封闭了,要到明天呢.
Lime tongue: Bad news!There's a blizzard!The roads are closed until tomorrow.
小流氓:噢…好啊!让我们疯起来吧!
Hooligan: Yeaaaah!Yeah!Let's get stupid!
凯特:什么?我现在就想快点回去.
Kate: That?And all I wanna do is get outta here.
迈克:凯特?凯特?恐怕我们要在这里再待一个晚上.
Mike: Kate?Kate?I am afraid we're sort of stuck in here another night.
凯特:什么???
Kate: What???
本:迈克,前台来电话了,说如果你要是再待一个晚上的话,
Ben: Mike, that was the front desk, they said if you stay another night,
得先付1000块的押金.迈克:啊,凯特?记得你说过,
they need a 1000 dollar deposit. Mike: Uh, Kate?
谁有钱谁付帐吗?00:22:37,500
Remember what you said about whoever has the money pays?